Guide to the Charles Laverty Papers AIA.074
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI. William V. Kennedy Papers, 1952-2002; 2.1 Linear Feet in 3 record cartons, 9 manuscript boxes, and 2 flat boxes
  William V. Kennedy (1928-2003) was a journalist and a faculty member at the United States Army War College in Carlisle, Pennsylvania. He worked as a journalist from 1951 until his death in 2003, and taught at the Army War College between 1967 and 1984. His writing focused on the military, military history, and the role of religion in the military. He founded the Thompson Battalion Memorial Project Committee in order to honor William Thompson, an officer in the Continental Army during the American Revolutionary War who lived in Carlisle, Pennsylvania.
  This series documents the career and research interests of William V. Kennedy, with material dating from the 1950s through the 2000s. Material includes scrapbooks, correspondence, and legal documents. The scrapbooks contain clippings of Kennedy's articles on the military, military history, and the role of religion, particularly Catholicism, in the military. Kennedy's correspondence documents his work as an instructor at the United States Army War College, his participation in the Thompson Battalion Memorial Project Committee, and the lawsuits he brought against the Army War College in the 1980s. The latter are supported by legal documents created through these suits.
  - Irish History Files, 1958-1999 (Box 6, Folder 23-37)
  - Subject Files, 1952-1990 (Box 14, Box 8-11)
  - Thompson Battalion Memorial Project Committee Files, 1985-2000 (Box 7, Folder 1-34, Box 8, Folder 1-29, Box 11, Folder 1-6, Box 122, Folder 18-19)
  - United States Army Files, 1953-1981 (Box 14, Folder 12, Box 15, Folder 1-6, Box 125, Folder 1-2)
  - United States Army War College Files, 1969-1985 (Box 11, Folder 7-12, Box 12, Folder 1-10, Box 13, Box 14, Folder 1-7)
  - Writings, 1952-2001 (Box 15, Folder 7-13, Box 16, Folder 1-9, Box 17, Folder 1-10, Box 18, Box 127, Folder 1-3)